MOJO MOJO MOJO SPY
This world is a riot of colors
Truth and lies confuse our eyes
Look with your heart and see
The truth is not far away
Hey you could do better
Truth and lies
Can't escape the grey smoke of the mind
Bring all your courage
And maybe save this world
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Sima Gang erupts!
How's the plan coming along?
Everything is going according to your wishes
I've found out everything
About the toys in Tuna Town
I'm sure the plan will be foolproof
We of the Golden Tooth Gang believe
Only with nonstop work
Can the Earth survive
But the pitiful people
Get two days off a week
And celebrate so many holidays
The worst part is...
These people even make all these toys
Just to rot people's minds from childhood
So our Gold Tooth Gang
Will strike and destroy Tuna Town's
Every festival
Every amusement facility
Every toy
This Toy Mobilization of ours
Will completely wake people up
Oh no
These gold-tooth crooks
Are going to cause trouble in Tuna Town
I have to notify Officer Han right away
To come and catch them all in one sweep
Han, Officer Han
Why are you so exhausted?
You got like this from messing around catching gold-tooths yesterday, right?
Officer Han
I found the gold-tooth crooks' hideout!
Where's the Big Gold Tooth?
There was definitely a big gold tooth here last night!
I think YOU have gold teeth in your brain!
I've decided
To punish you by suspending you from duty today
Reflect properly right here
Tomorrow, don't mention any gold teeth to me again.
I'm heading off now.
今天镇上的玩具店
Got a big shipment of new stock in.
There must be a lot of people.
I have to get back to maintain order.
Don't come making things worse.
Aw, so comfy~
Don't want gold teeth, don't want gold teeth
Toys....
These people also made so many toys
让 人们 从小 就 玩物丧志
This time, we're doing Toy Story.
It'll definitely shake people wide awake.
Today the toy store in town got a big shipment of new stuff.
The plan is foolproof.
Tuna Town Toy Store
I'm not imagining things.
There really are bad guys going after the toy store.
Let me go!
Grandma,
You got a Shar-Pei with a gold tooth?
Hey, that's my dear mommy you're talking about!
She likes Shar Pei dogs.
Your mom looks about the same age as you,
I look like I'm seventy
But I'm actually only seven
Because I have an aging disease
What are you doing here?
I'm doing a jigsaw puzzle
But no matter what, I can't put it together
So I'm going to kill myself
Little girl
I'll help you!
Great!
Help me hang from that tree!
No!
I'll just help you with the puzzle instead
You're so nice, big brother!
There are three thousand pieces here
Three thousand!
Finally finished!
Hahaha, I'm wiped out!
Can't fall down...
Can't fall down!
Big brother
Try on this pair!
Not bad!
It's eco-friendly and saves money!
I still have urgent business today
I'll play with you another day.
Bye-bye, big brother!
Don't run!
Give me back my toy
Stop him!
Quick, stop him, Officer Han!
My toys!
Who's watching the shop?
Uh oh, this is bad!
Hurry up.
Destroy him!
Don't mention the gold tooth.
Little girl.
不 金牙教母 你还是束手就擒 安享晚年吧
Hahaha! You little brat! Watch the Golden Tooth Gang's ultimate move!
The brain-dead gold-tooth laser that's already dropped your IQ by 60!
Awesome!
乖宝宝 出来吧 游戏结束了
Take this!
No!
You defended the people's right to happiness.
Mm, all done.
Awesome!
【Ending Theme】
Look at tomorrow, waving to me at the horizon.
Every day, sunrise and sunset, spinning through time, dreaming of more
Awaiting every second, every moment of life
Bright eyes are sparkling
A smile that basks in the sun
Stomping through the screaming crossroads